스트라이크 백 지난 이야기
20과엔 새 리더가 필요하다
Section 20 requires new leadership.
Some of you already
know Captain Dalton.
달튼 대위를 아는 사람도 있으리라 본다
Michael Stonebridge, you
must miss it, in the field?
마이클 스톤브리지
현장이 그립겠어
오늘 밤, 제군들은 실탄을 사용한다
Tonight you'll be
employing libe rounds.
Get down!
사상자 발생!
What happened
to your brother--
동생에게 무슨 일이 생긴 거죠?
His name was Jake.
He was a fine soldier.
제이큽니다. 좋은 병사였죠
케이스에 뭐 들었는데?
What's in the case?
핵폭탄 기폭장치
Nuclear triggers.
do you have any idea what
possession of those triggers
그게 나쁜 사람 손에 들어가면 어떤 일이 생길지 상상이나 가나?
could mean in the wrong hands?
Can we start again?
다시 시작할 수 있을까?
Of course we can.
당연히 있지
Kerry!
캐리!
Craig Hanson as the man
who murdered your wife.
크레이그 핸슨이 당신 부인을 죽인 범인이야
- Conrad Knox.
- That is our new target?
콘래드 녹스
저 아저씨가 새 타겟이라고?
He could certainly
afford those triggers.
그자라면 충분히 기폭장치를 다룰 수 있습니다
With this...We can raise Africa
이 핵폭탄이 있으면 아프리카의 말을 귀담아 들을 수밖에 없을 게야
to where its voice is not
just heard, but listened to.
포로 처리에 대한 명확한 규정이 있습니다!
There are clear guidelines
about the treatment of prisoners.
Craig Hanson, Mr. Knox.
크레이그 핸슨입니다
Hire him.
고용하게
다른 폭탄까지 정확히 동시에 해제하지 않으면 기폭되고 말 거야
If we deactivate this one
without doing the other one
at exactly the same
time, it'll detonate.
널 용서해
I forgive you.
This isn't about Africa.
This is about you.
아프리카 문제가 아닙니다. 당신 문제였죠
이!
일
영!
Fuck me.
존 나
안돼!
No!
소령님이 맞았습니다!
Dalton has been shot.
Section 20 has a future after all.
20과 폐지는 면했군
It's a good thing
there was two of you.
자네 둘이 있어 다행이야
레바논 베카 계곡
- Please...
- Shut up!
-제발
-닥쳐!
- 닥쳐!
- 닥치고 있어!
실수하시는 겁니다, 말 했잖아요!
전 기잡니다, 생사람 잡는 거라구요!
You are making a mistake.
I have told you, I am a journalist.
The woman you were
with... a journalist, too?
같이 있던 여자는? 거기도 기자야?
I don't know who you mean.
누구 말입니까
Don't you know what
we do with spies?
스파이를 어떻게 처리하는지 아나?
전 연합통신사 기자라구요!
신원 확인해 보십시오!!
You are making a mistake.
I am Associated Press.
Check my credentials!
Where is the woman?
여자 어디있어?
좆 까라
멈춰. 멈춰!
Kamali.
카말리? 알 주하리께선...
내 말이 곧 알 주하리의 말이다
잘 새겨 들어
이 놈은 안 불 거야
이러고 있을 시간도 없고
실수하는 겁니다. 전 기자란 말입니다
You are making a mistake.
I am a journalist.
I know who you are, Sgt. Baxter.
네 정체를 나는 알아. 벡스터 하사
I know everything.
난 전부 알고 있어
미국 캘리포니아 북부
영국에는 스누커라는 이런 비슷한 게임이 있는데
in Britain, we have
a game called Snooker,
which is similar in
many ways; it just, uh,
requires a more skillful
and delicate touch.
더 높은 기술과 더 섬세한 조작을 필요로하지
테이블도 더 크고 포켓도 더 많고...
It's also played on a larger
table with much smaller pockets,
so this is, um, easy.
그러니까 이 정도는...
쉽지
You served?
- 복무했었나?
- 아뇨, 회계삽니다
No, ma'am. I'm an accountant.
You boys wear it like a badge.
군인은 딱 보면 티가 나
I'm on holiday.
예 휴가나왔습니다
How far are you going?
- 어디까지 가?
- 길 끝까지 가보려고요
Until we run out of road.
May you find peace
at the end of it.
종국에는 평안을 찾길
Cheers to that.
평안을 찾길
Oh, fuck me.
스...바 역시 미국애들이 최고다
I love American girls.
Where's that buddy of yours at?
네 친구는 어디갔지?
You should probably ask that
pretty waitress of yours.
여기 예쁘장한 종업원이랑 있을 걸요?
That's my daughter!
걔 내 딸이야!
"Let's have some fun," You said,
좀 즐기자고 그렇게 성화더니 꼴 좋군 좋아
"Let's get away from it all,"
You said, yeah. Brilliant.
Michael, you wanted to
go for a fuckin' walk.
네가 가자던 산책보다는 나아
Mate, the Camino de
Santiago's not a walk,
카미노 데 산티아고는 산책길이 아냐
영적 순례길이지
it's a spiritual
pilgrimage. I told you that.
Hey, you boys, you know that
California's a helmet state, right?
거기 너네!
캘리포니아에선 헬멧 써야되는 거 알아 몰라?!
No, sir, we weren't aware of that.
아뇨, 경관님. 몰랐습니다
- I was.
- Really?
- 난 알고 있었어...
- 진짜?
And you got traffic violations
교통 위반을 여기부터 알래스카까지 6개 주에 걸쳐 했구만
in 6 other states
from here to Alaska.
Only 6?
- 6개 밖에 안 되네?
- 더 정진해야겠는데?
You runnin' from somethin'?
어디 도망이라도 가나?
아뇨, 그냥... 휴일을 보내고 있습니다.
Uh, we're just on holiday, sir.
- Vacation.
휴가
- 네, 휴가요
- 휴가를 말하는 겁니다
He means vacation.
License and registration.
면허증이랑 등록증 좀 보지
Does that belong to you?
저것도 몰고 오셨습니까?
Is that Richmond?
리치몬드지?
Fucking Richmond.
리치몬드야
They're definitely with us.
- 아, 우리 거였네요
- 이봐!
See ya, man.
수고하십시오
Stand to, Sergeants. Leave is over.
임무다, 하사들
휴가는 끝이야
- What's going on?
- What're you talking about? We just got here!
- 무슨 일이야?
- 뭐야 방금 여기 왔는데?!
Come on, Michael.
Back me up on this.
어서, 마이클. 지원 좀 해봐
- Look, we're heading south. We have plans.
- Not anymore!
우리 막 남쪽으로 가고 있는 참인데, 일정 다 짜놨다고
- 일정 따위 버려
- 왜?
- Why?
- What happened?
무슨 일인데?
Baxter's dead!
벡스터가 죽었어!
- What? How?
- Come on.
뭐?
어떻게?
타기나 해
Briefing en route.
- 브리핑은 가면서 한다
- 잠깐!
Wait!
Transport waiting at
Twentynine Palms airbase.
수송편은 29 팜즈 공군기지에 현재 대기중!
I got a situation here.
상황발생!
레바논 베이루트
Shit.
제기랄!
나가
나가!
Not you, Sankara, you sack of shit!
넌 말고 산차이, 이 개새끼야
You betrayed me.
- 날 배신했겠다?
- 아냐, 맹세해!
No! I swear!
They murdered one of my men.
그놈이 내 부하를 죽였어
You give me Kamali,
당장 카말리를 안 내놓으면
네놈이 내 끄나풀인 걸 헤즈볼라가 알게 될 거야
or Hezbollah finds out
that you're working for me.
But I'm
not--
난 네 끄나풀이...
You better hope they think so.
그렇게 생각하는 게 차라리 나을 거야!
Colombia! They went to Colombia!
콜롬비아! 콜롬비아로 갔어!
콜롬비아 어디?!
Colombia's a big fucking place!
Kamali's meeting the Gomez
Cartel and the Russians!
카말리는 고메즈 카르텔이랑 러시아인들이랑 만나기로 했어
They're about to go to war!
전쟁을 벌이려는 중이야!
Put some fucking clothes
on. You're disgusting.
옷이나 입어 이 역겨운 새끼야
Ready, Sergeant.
- 준비 됐습니까?
- 뭐예요? 설마 엉덩이에 놓을 거?
What is that you're
gonna put in my ass?
Yellow fever, tetanus, typhoid.
황열병, 파상풍, 장티푸스...
You're going into
Colombian jungle, Sergeant.
콜롬비아 정글로 가잖습니까?
You're gonna be dodging
more than bullets.
총 맞는 것보다 병 걸려 죽을 확률이 높을 걸요
그렇게 말하신다면야
자, 준비됐습니다
Seein' as you asked so
nicely, Doc, here you go, man.
Here we go.
네, 갑니다
That wasn't gel.
- 따...끔하구만!
- 누가 최곱니까?
Who's your daddy now?
Major Dalton, they're
ready for the briefing now.
달튼 소령님, 브리핑 준비 됐습니다
Welcome back, Sergeants.
복귀 환영하네, 제군들
I presume you've
heard about Baxter.
벡스터 일은 들었겠지
Yes, ma'am.
네 들었습니다
We will have time to mark
his death, but as it stands,
벡스터를 추모할 시간은 분명 있을 테지만
벡스터를 죽인 놈을 잡을 시간은 현재 너무도 촉박한 상황이다
we only have a small window of
time to catch the fuck who did it.
Richmond...Whitehall online yet?
리치몬드, 화이트홀과 연결은 아직인가?
Coming up now, Major.
됐습니다 소령님
They're ready for you, sir.
준비 됐습니다 중령님
Major.
소령
Gentlemen.
제군들
- Shit.
- Good evening, Colonel.
- 뭐...? 필립 로크잖아
- 안녕하십니까 중령님
- That's Philip Locke.
- What, you know him?
- 아는 사람이야?
- 아니, 알기는 아는데 만나본 적은 없어
No. I know of him.
- Never met.
- Headlines only.
다 과장일 뿐일세
While you two were away
on your little soiree,
자네들이 잠깐 파티를 즐기는 동안
an operation in Beirut
went badly wrong.
베이루트에서 작전이 완전히 틀어졌네
Sgt. Baxter's
killer is this man--
벡스터를 죽인 건 이 자다
Leo Kamali.
리오 카말리
레바논계 영국 국적자고
He's a British national,
Lebanese heritage.
Kamali is the money man of
the Al-Zuhari terror network
알 주하리 테러 네트워크의 돈줄이자 수석 참모다
and the brains of the operation.
Thanks to Kamali, Al-Zuhari
and his organization control
알 주하리의 코카인과 헤로인 대부분이
이 자의 지휘 하에 유럽으로 유통되고 있다
the supply of most of the cocaine
and heroin going into Europe.
Dalton and Baxter were
tracking him, and, uh, well...
달튼 소령과 벡스터 하사가 이 자를 추적하고 있었지만...
흠...
care to embellish, Major?
더 상세하게 말해보겠나?
Low-level surveillance,
intelligence-gathering.
근접 감시와 정보 수집이었습니다
We got made somehow.
- 어떻게든... 해냈습니다
- 좀 꺼줘...
Can you turn that off?
We get Kamali, we
get Al-Zuhari himself.
카말리를 잡으면 알 주하리까지 잡을 수 있다
He's the ultimate
target of this mission,
알 주하리가 이 미션의 최종 목표다
and we've never had a
chance to get to him before,
지금까지 없었던 기회야
until now.
We have no current intelligence
on Al-Zuhari's whereabouts,
알 주하리의 최근 거취에 관해서는 아무런 정보가 없지만
소령 덕에 카말리가 보가타에 있다는 것은 알게 됐다
but thanks to Major Dalton, we
know Kamali's currently in Bogota,
but our chance to
get him is limited.
하지만 잡기 쉽지는 않지
Colombia is still its usual
mess of corruption and violence.
콜롬비아에는 아직도 부패와 폭력이 만연합니다
Cartels still have
politicians and police
정계와 경찰력에 카르텔의 수하들이 널려있고요
거긴 믿을 사람이 없습니다
on the payroll, so there
is no trusting anyone.
Except this woman.
이 한 명 빼곤
That's Kim Martinez, a DEA agent
킴 마르티네즈
마약단속국 요원으로 정글에서 작은 팀을 운영하고 있지
running a small narco unit
in the jungle near an area
카르텔 두목 미겔 고메즈의 영역 인근이야
controlled by cartel
boss Miguel Gomez.
He's the man Kamali's gonna meet.
카말리가 그자를 만날 걸세
I've worked with Martinez
before. She's good.
마르티네즈 요원과 일해 봐서 아는데 꽤 유능한 요원이네
매우 유능하지
She's very good.
She'll take you to him.
자네들을 잘 도와줄 걸세
Richmond'll set up the Mobile
Crib at Bogota Air Force base.
리치몬드는 보고타 공군 기지에 작전실을 구축하도록
Questions?
질문 있나?
Yeah. You want him dead or alive?
- 생포합니까 사살합니까?
- 생포한다
We want Kamali alive.
With his intel, we could cripple
Al-Zuhari's entire network.
카말리의 정보로 알 주하리 네트워크를 전부 쓸어버릴 수 있다
Agreed.
그렇지
But if capture's not an option...
하지만 생포가 불가능하다면
kill him.
사살하게
- Roger that.
- Yes, sir.
- 알겠습니다
- 네 알겠습니다
The holiday's over, lads.
휴가는 끝났네 제군들
Good luck.
행운을 비네
Oh, and, Major Dalton,
달튼 소령?
you know I've been
looking for an excuse
내가 현장에 갈 변명거리만 찾고 있었던 거 잘 알테지?
to get some dust on my boots.
Don't give me one.
그런 일 없도록 하게
No, sir.
네 알겠습니다
If they're bringing Locke
into this, it's serious shit.
로크가 지휘하는 일이면 이건 심각한 일이야
Yeah? What's his story?
그래? 뭐 하는 사람인데?
Philip Locke. He's a
Special Forces legend.
필립 로크. 특수부대 전설이야
When I trained at Hereford, he
was the man we all wanted to be.
연대 대원들 모두의 우상이었지
He's served in every major
theater for the last 3 decades.
30년 동안 주요 전장은 다 돌아다녔어
Rumor has it he was
one of the men who
듣기로는 지브롤터에서 IRA를 추적한 것도 그 사람이라더군
went after the IRA on Gibraltar.
Got it.
그러냐
Do you think they're
ready for this?
두 하사 준비는 좀 된 것 같나?
카르텔은 만만한 상대가 아냐
The cartels don't screw around.
How are they looking?
상태 어때?
Better than you, ma'am.
소령님보다는 양호합니다
- 우리 지금쯤 바하에서 데킬라 마시고 있어야 하는데!
- 내말이 말야!!
We should be fuckin' slammin'
tequilas in Baja right now.
Don't tell me that, Michael!
Shit.
The plan was always to
come back to Twenty, right?
어쨌든 20으로 돌아올 계획이었잖아, 그지?
Mike?
마이크?
See you on the ground.
밑에서 보자
See ya round.
또봐~
Go on. Say something.
그래
말해
Zero, this is Bravo team.
본부 여기는 브라보 팀
On the ground... finally.
착지했다
마침내
Zero, this is Bravo team.
본부, 여기는 브라보 팀. 들리나?
Do you read me?
- You got anything?
- Nothing.
- 뭐 들려?
- 아니
- Cartel must be jamming the signal.
- Yeah.
- 카르텔이 전파를 교란하고 있는 거야
- 그래
Movin' out.
이동하자
콜롬비아 카케타
니미럴
- Mike.
- Yeah?
마이키!
쌍
콜롬비아 보고타 공군 기지
Corporal.
상병! 아직인가?
Are we up yet?
통신 연결에 20분 정도 걸릴 것 같습니다
Got comms online in 20 minutes.
- What's the problem?
- Signal issues.
- 문제가 뭔가?
- 신호 이상입니다
- 어서 해결해
- 알겠습니다
- Get it sorted.
- Yes, ma'am.
크립 가동시켜
I need the Crib operational.
Scott and Stonebridge are
in country and need support.
스콧과 스톤브리지는 지원이 필요한 곳에 있다
I want their location
and I want radio contact.
위치 추적하고 통신 연결 실시해
Dropped into some
shit hole like this.
이런 똥통에 빠트려 놓다니
Fuckin' God knows
what diseases around.
무슨 병이 있을지 신도 모를 이런 곳에
Pick some bad-ass hombre,
나쁜놈 좀 잡으라고
and for what?
대체 뭐땀시?
World's just gonna keep on turnin',
세상은 돌고 또 도는데
and some asshole's
just gonna replace him.
잡아도 어차피 또 딴 놈이 대신할 건데
We're in the bad-ass
hombre-making business, buddy.
우리 완전 나쁜놈 생성 사업 하고 있는 거야
Fuckin' job creators.
일자리나 창출하고 있다고
Ours is not to reason why.
우리가 이유를 물을 위치는 아니잖아
이젠 좀 물어야 될 지도
Well, maybe it's time we start.
I'm gettin' sick of this shit.
존나 이 짓도 지겨워
I just want to
fuckin' win, you know?
그냥 이기고 싶다고
There's no win. You
know that. We still--
그런 거 없다는 거 알잖아? 우리 아직...
What the fuck was that?
뭐였지 시발?
- Probably a candiru.
- What the fuck's that?
- 칸디루일지도 몰라
- 그게 뭐야 시발?
The little fish that swims up
your cock and drinks your blood.
음경으로 들어가서 피 빨아먹는 물고기
You can't get it
out. It's got barbs.
빼내지도 못해. 가시가 있거든
You fuckin' kiddin' me?
- 구라 아냐? 시발?
- 아냐
- No, mate.
- We get a vaccine for that?
우리 그거 예방접종 맞았어?
걱정마 스콧
Nothin' to worry about, mate,
'cause it'll never
find your tiny cock.
네 고추는 너무 작아서 걔네가 찾을 수도 없을 테니까
Fuck you.
좆까!
I want to get out now.
나 나갈래
Bravo, this is Zero.
Radio check, over.
브라보 여기는 본부, 들리나, 오버?
On it. Bravo, this is Zero.
켜
브라보 여기는 본부, 들리나, 오버?
Radio check, over.
Zero, this is Bravo Team.
본부 여기는 브라보 팀, 신호가 잘 안잡힌다, 오버
Difficult radio check, over.
We can track you, but clear
comms are gonna be hard.
위치 추적 가능하나 수월한 통신은 어렵겠다
You're two clicks south of
the rendezvous with Martinez.
마티네즈와 만나기로 한 장소에서 2km 밖에 있다
Good bearing.
방향은 양호하다
누가 배신했어?
Who betrayed us?
누가 배신했어?!
Get up, you bitch!
이리와 개새끼야!
A name.
이름!
That's all I want from you.
이름만 말해! 이름!
A name.
이름 말해
좆 까!
Colonel, what does the name
Sebastian Gray mean to you?
중령님, 세바스찬 그레이란 이름 아십니까?
Gray?
그레이?
MI6와 일하던 자였어
Well, he was with MI6.
He worked out of the Beirut
consulate in the eighties,
80년대에 베이루트 영사관 밖에서 일했었는데
불러들였더니 그 길로 사라졌어
but when they recalled
him, he vanished.
Up until two years ago,
2년 전까지 최고 입찰자에게 정보를 팔고 있었지
he was selling intel
to the highest bidder,
but then went to ground when
he pissed off the French.
그러다가 프랑스인들 열 받게 하고는 잠적했네
They sent a team in to get
him. We thought he was dead.
그 자를 잡으러 팀을 보냈다기에 죽은 줄 알았는데
Yeah, well, I have a pretty
strong feeling he isn't.
죽은 게 아닌 것 같습니다
그레이를 찾아야겠습니다
Need to find him.
Well, I'll send you what we can,
but it's past its sell-by date.
있는 건 다 보내주겠네만
시일이 좀 된 것들이야
And if you do find him,
approach from downwind.
찾게되면 먼저 낌새 못 차리게 조심하게
He sees you first, you've lost him.
낌새 차리면 바로 뜰 거야
Get me on the next
flight to Beirut.
- 베이루트행 비행기 예약하게
- 알겠습니다
Right away, sir.
안녕하십니까
안녕하신가
Are you alone?
혼자십니까?
Hands up.
손 들어
- I take it that weapon's not for fishing.
- Protection.
- 낚시하는데 무기가 왜 필요하지?
- 내 몸은 내가 지켜야지
Around here, you never
know when some dumb gringo
웬 미국놈이 정글에서 튀어나올지 알 수 없거든
will come out of the jungle.
Perhaps I should
introduce my friends, huh?
자, 이제 내 친구들을 소개해줘야겠지?
Gentlemen.
아, 네
You're late.
늦었잖아
I thought there was two of you.
- 두 명인 줄 알았는데?
- ...저기 있네
There is.
Kim Martinez.
킴 마르티네즈
Even lovelier in the flesh.
실물이 훨씬 낫네
Don't try that charm shit on me.
수작 부리지 마
This one talk?
- 말도 할 줄 아나?
- 할 말이 있을 때는요
When I have something to say, yeah.
So you're Colonel
Locke's team, huh?
니들이 로크 중령 팀이라 이거지
Well, we better get you
briefed before you go
정글에 누구한테 또 걸리기 전에 브리핑 좀 해줘야겠군
stumbling into somebody
else in the jungle.
Not everybody's as
warm-hearted as me.
나처럼 봐주는 사람도 없을 테니까 말이야
I like her.
괜찮은데?
You would.
그러시겠지
Listen, if you boys want Kamali,
잘 들어.
카말리를 잡으려면 이 놈 옆에서 뺴와야 할 거야
you're going to have to
take him from this guy--
Miguel Gomez,
미겔 고메즈
전직 콜럼비아 경찰관
former Colombian police commander.
He changed sides?
- 편을 바꿨군요
- 돈이라면 뭔들 못해
Money'll do that.
Now, Gomez was a brutal cop,
경찰 때도 부패 경찰이었지만 지금은 벌이는 판이 달라
현재 고메즈는 카르텔 조직을 운영하고 있다
but he is in a whole 'nother
league now he's
running his own cartel.
He calls himself "The Jaguar."
자기를 재규어라고 부르지
All this is his.
여기가 전부 고메즈 영역이야
경비가 삼엄하고 순찰도 돌지
It's heavily guarded and patrolled,
but Colonel Locke tells me
you guys get the job done,
로크 중령이 너네 꽤 유능하다고 하던데
operating behind the lines.
특히 적진 내에서
Yep, that's us.
- 예, 그렇죠
- 안팎이 있었어?
There's a line?
Kamali's here only
once or twice a year,
카말리는 여기 일 년에 한두 번 온다
and we know he's key to
카르텔 자금을 해외로 빼내는 핵심 인물이야
moving the cartel's
money out of the country.
Now Gomez has called together all
현재 고메즈가 러시아 무기 거래상과의 만남을 위해
카르텔 보스들을 전부 소집한 상태다
the cartel bosses to meet
with a Russian arms dealer.
My guess--it was
on Kamali's orders.
내 생각엔
전부 카말리의 지시야
Gomez's place is
two clicks southeast.
여기서 남동쪽으로 2km가 고메즈의 본거지다
- 작전 초소 구축해보고... 해질 때까지 기다리자
- 좋은 계획이네
Find a suitable
O.P., wait till dark.
Sounds like a plan.
Leo.
- 레오!
- 미겔, 내 친구
Miguel, my friend.
반갑네. 너무 오랜만이군
It's good to see you.
It's been too long.
Seems like you only come to see
me now when there are problems.
이제 무슨 문제가 생겨야만 보는 것 같군 그래
Are they all here?
- 다들 왔나?
- 자네만 기다리고 있어
You're the last.
I have entertainment.
집에 예쁜 여자 천지 널렸는데
이렇게 데려올 필요 없는데 말이야
You didn't need to bring
your own puta madre.
Her name is Celine, Miguel,
셀린느는 내 여자야 미겔
애들 데리고 놀라고 데려온 게 아냐
and she is not for The Jaguar.
- Viktor?
- Yeah, Viktor is here,
- 빅토르?
- 그래, 아르카디 대신 빅토르가 왔어
not Arkady.
He can make it a problem.
- 문제의 소지가 되나?
- 여기 불만 있는 사람 안 그래도 많아
We have a lot of
unhappy people here, Leo.
조련사를 기다렸는데
원숭이가 아니라
We expected the organ
grinder, not the monkey.
Sometimes the monkey
is easier to control.
구슬리기에는 그래도 원숭이가 쉬운 법이지
Viktor, you remember my friend Leo.
- 빅토르, 카말리 씨 기억하지?
- 안녕하쇼
I do.
Do remember me to your father.
자넬 보니 자네 아버지가 생각나는군. 참 대단한 분이셨지
여기 못오셨다니 아쉽네
He is a great man.
It's a shame he couldn't be here.
제가 아버지를 대변하고 있습니다. 모든 문제에서요
I speak for my
father in all things.
들어오게
Is there a problem, soldier?
뭐 문제 있나, 하사?
Candiru.
칸디루...
거시기에 들어가는 좆만한 물고기...
You know, those little
fish that swim up--
Not here.
여기 없어
It's the Amazon.
아마존에나 있지
Asshole.
개섀끼!
I shouldn't be here.
내가 여기 있어선 안 되는 거야
I shouldn't have to be here,
여기 있어야 될 이유도 없었어야 해
and that I am must surely tell us
그러니 뭔가가 분명히 잘못됐다는 것을 알 수 있지
that something is
not as it should be.
Our activities
우리 사업이 전에 없는 정밀 조사를 받고 있다
are under more scrutiny
than ever before.
Every agency, every police force
모든 기관과 경찰들이 우리를 잡으려고 혈안이야
bring their strength against us,
and yet we prevail.
그럼에도 불구하고 우리가 승리하고 있지
How?
왜?
우리는 단결하고 있으니까
Because we are
united in our efforts.
Division will destroy us.
분열은 곧 죽음이다
Lack of trust will destroy us,
신뢰의 결핍 또한 죽음이지
본인은 절대
용납하지 않는다
and I will not tolerate it.
Al-Zuhari will not tolerate it.
알 주하리 역시
용납하지 않는다
Who says crime doesn't pay, huh?
누가 범죄는 이익이 안 된다고 했어?
I got 4 on the towers.
- 감시탑에 4명 있어
- 밑에는 최소 6명 확인
I got at least 6 on the ground.
Am I right in believing
that Samuel has paid you
자네가 일 주일 전에 배달하기로 한 무기
사뮤엘이 대금을 전부 지불한 게 맞나?
for the arms shipment which you
agreed to deliver a week ago?
You know where your fucking ship is
화물이 왜 안 온지는 네놈도 잘 알 텐데!
and you know why it's not here.
Leo, you talk about respect?
레오, 당신이 존중을 입에 담습니까?
Two of my best men killed, huh?!
내 심복 두 명이 죽었습니다!
Is this true?
사실인가?
Samuel says that the russians
러시아인들이 사뮤엘의 창녀 하나를 강간하고 죽였다는군
그래서 죽였다고 하는군
raped and murdered
one of his whores
and he had them killed in return.
- Martinez.
- Hmm?
- 마르티네즈?
- 응?
Want to take out the
guards, cover our exfil?
우리가 보초를 처리할 테니까 퇴출 좀 커버해줄래?
Why don't I just go in and
grab Kamali for you, too?
너네 대신 내가 카말리라도 잡아주길 바라는 거야 뭐야?
퇴출 시 교란만 좀 해주시면 좋겠습니다
A distraction for our
exfil will be great.
You got it.
알았다
"You got it."
아 라 따
He gets "You got it"?
쟤한텐 알았다 그러고?!
He's polite.
쟤는 공손하잖아
Besides, that British
accent kills me.
게다가 내가 영국 억양을 좀 좋아하거든
There is a way for
us to make a peace,
평화를 이룩하는 방법이 있지
but it is through
sacrifice that we progress.
그걸 위해서라면 희생은 불가피하네
Of course, Viktor,
빅토르 자네는 물건을 배달하도록 하게
you will deliver the shipment.
I'll ensure Arkady will
hear of your diplomacy,
약속컨대 춘부장께서 자네의 외교술에 무척 대견해 하실 걸세
and he'll be proud of his son.
Samuel...
- 사뮤엘...
- 저런 새끼랑은 거래 안 할...
Hey, I'm not going
to do a fucking...
자네는 자네 행동에 대해 죄값을 치르고
You will make redress
for your actions,
우리 모두는 존중에 대해 다시금 깨치게 될 걸세
and we will all
learn a new respect.
여기서 치워!
So let's go in soft,
let's grab Kamali,
조용히 침투해서
카말리만 잡아서 뜨자
and let's leave, try
not to start a war here.
전쟁 일으키지 말고
Copy that.
접수 완료
Stop it!
그만!
Stop. Hold on.
그만... 잠깐!
Damien.
데미안!
Rebecca.
레베카
What the fuck are you doing here?
뭐 하고 있는 거야 지금
What do you think I'm doing here?
뭐 하고 있는 거 같아?
You said you were out.
접는다며?
You said no more
Mossad, no more killing!
모사드 안 할 거라며?
암살 끝이라며!
I gave you that out!
내가 구실까지 줬는데!
Did you really believe
it was gonna be that easy?
- 그게 그렇게 쉽게 될 거라 생각했어?
- 맙소사
Jesus Christ.
This is what we do.
이게 우리 일이야!
And you?
그러는 너는?
I'm here for Leo Kamali.
- 난 카말리 잡으러 왔어
- 하
Ha.
"Ha."
아하?
뭔 뜻이야 그건?
What's that mean?
Gracias, brother, gracias.
Kamali's mine.
- 카말리는 내 꺼야
- 좆 까
Bullshit.
Do you have any idea what I had
to do to get close to this guy?
- 카말리한테 접근하기 위해 내가 무슨 짓을 했는지 알기나 해?
- 그래 딱 보니 알겠네, 레베카
Yeah, I got a pretty
fair idea, Rebecca.
Do you even know who he is?
- 그가 누군지 알기나 해?
- 당연히 알지, 알라의 돈줄이야
Yeah, of course I do.
He's Allah's banker.
So why do you think I'm here?
그럼 내가 왜 여기 있는 거 같아?
What? So Mossad can disappear him?
모사드가 처리하시려고 아냐?
Fuck that. He killed one of ours.
좆까. 그새끼가 우리 팀원을 죽였어
그새낀 내 꺼야
I'm taking him.
Damien,
데미, 이 일 망치지 마
이제 조금만 있으면-
do not fuck this up.
I am this close to
getting somethi...
- Celine?
- Fuck.
셀린느?
Celine?
You locked the door?
문 잠갔어?
I don't like how these
bodyguards look at me.
여기 경호원들이 날 보는 게 싫어요
They make me feel like
one of those cheap hookers.
싸구려 창녀가 된 기분이 든단 말이에요
I don't like these
people any more than you.
나도 여기 인간들이 싫지만 어쩔 수가 없어
It's necessary.
I will make it up to you.
꼭 보상해 줄게
I promise.
약속해
지금은 말고요
나중에
I love it when you speak Arabic.
당신이 아랍어로 말할 때가 좋아
No.
어이
Buenas noches.
좋은 밤
What is this, a
fuckin' family reunion?
뭐야 이거, 망할 가족 상봉이라도 해?
Pretty harsh.
- 너무 냉혹한가?
- 별로
Not really.
Want to get dressed?
옷 안 입을 거야?
- You're making a big mistake.
- Shut him up.
- 자네들 큰 실수를 저지르는 거야
- 입 막아
You don't know what you're doing.
네가 무슨 짓을 하고 있는지 넌 몰라
No, he just makes it look that way.
아냐, 쟤 그냥 그렇게 보이는 거 뿐이야
내 말 들어야 해
You have to listen
to me. You have--
내 말...!
No, I don't.
필요 없어
- 거기서 뭐 해?!
- 아 제기랄
Oh, shit.
나와!
No, no, no, no, no.
잠깐, 잠깐...
진정해
나 너네 편이야
The fuck you wearing?
뭐 입고 있는 거야?
You think I brought my fatigues?
군복이라도 가져왔을 거 같애?
This the exit.
- 여기로 나가야 해
- 마르티네즈가 일만 잘 해놨으면
As long as Locke's little
buddy's done her job.
Delta, need that distraction.
델타, 교란책 준비 됐나?
You can't do this. Kamali's mine.
이럴 순 없어, 카말리는 내 꺼야
Unless you got a
Mossad team out there
밖에 있는 청개구리들이 모사드가 아닌 이상
카말리는 우리 거야
disguised as tree frogs,
he's ours. Oh, yeah.
아, 얘가 말 안 해줬지?
얘 이스라엘 비밀요원이야
It's always the little things
they don't tell you, huh?
Like she's an Israeli agent?
Delta, come in, Delta. Delta,
how about that distraction?
델타 나와라, 델타. 교란책은 어떻게 됐나?
Delta, come in. Do you copy?
델타 나와라, 들리나?
Delta, respond.
델타 응답하라
Nothing.
안되겠어
Scott, moving.
스콧, 이동
Oy, come here!
어이, 이리와!
What the fuck?!
- 뭐야, 썅!
- 이리 와!
- Come here.
- Do you know who the fuck I am?!
- 내가 누군지 알아?
- 누군지 상관 없어. 이리 와
I don't care who you
are. Come here, mate.
Don't!
Moving.
이동!
Fuck.
쌍!
Follow me, follow me! Move!
따라와, 따라와
이동!!
Just follow me, just follow me!
뒤로 숨어, 뒤로 숨어!
Viktor!
빅토르! 빅토르!
Viktor.
빅토르...
놈들을 잡아!!
이리로
계속 가
숙여, 숙여!
거기 있어!
You remember whose
side you're on, huh?
누꿀 쏴야 되는지 알긴 알지?
All right, you guys got
to start moving! Move!
- 마이키, 준비됐어? 나 간다!
- 가!
Go!
가!
- Who the hell is that?
- It's a long story. Move!
- 쟤는 누구야?!
- 말하기 깁니다, 가요!
Moving.
이동!
Excuse me. Excuse me.
실례합니다, 실례합니다
Damn it!
제길!
The only way you leave here
네가 여길 벗어날 수 있는 길은
머리에 총알 박히는 길 밖에 없으니까 어서 걸어. 걸어!!
is with a bullet in your head.
Now fucking move.
Move!
Don't shoot.
쏘지 마요
They haven't made us yet.
우릴 못 봤어요
Oh, God.
- 맙소사...
- 이봐요, 이봐요! 이리와요!
Come here!
Martinez!
마르티네즈!
- 마르티네즈!!
- 이동!
-Move!
-Fuck!
Rebecca! Down there!
- 레베카! 아래로!
- 맙소사...!
- Oh, God.
- Halt!
멈춰!
Martinez!
마르티네즈! 이리 와요! 어서!!
Come here! Come here!
Come here!
이리 와요!!
- 씹!
- 이리와!
Follow me!
교전!!
Martinez! Get back here!
- 마르티네즈!! 돌아와!!
- 이동!!
- Moving!
- Fuck!
Mikey! 9 o'clock
마이키, 9시 방향!
Fuck! Scott, moving!
스콧, 이동!
Grenade!
수류탄 투척!
Good work.
Bravo One. Do you copy?
브라보 원, 들리나? 여기는 브라보 원, 나와라
This is Brave One. Come in.
Zero, we need an exfil now.
본부, 지금 당장 퇴출이 필요하다
Nothing.
연결이 안돼
- Fuck.
- We're on our own.
우리끼리 해결해야 해
Stay down.
숙이고 있어!
탄창교체!
Mike! More coming on the ridge!
- 마이크! 산등성이로 적 출현!
- 확인!
Catch it!
탄창교체!
- 씹! 적 출현! 기관총이다!!
- 숨어 숨어 숨어!!!!
Fuck! Told you I
couldn't cover 'em!
Move! Move! Move! Down!
제길!
Oh! Michael!
- 마이클!
- 왜!
Yeah?
You Navy boys like to swim, right?
너네 해군들 수영 좋아하지?
Yeah.
You want to go get that boat?
저 보트 포획하고 싶지 않아?
Yeah, let's do it!
What the hell? Why not?
그래 해보자! 까짓거
Rebecca! You cover us back there!
레베카! 저기서 엄호해!
What the hell is he doing?
- 쟤 뭐하냐?
- 용감한 짓이거나 멍청한 짓이거나
Something brave or
something stupid.
Can't tell yet.
나도 몰라
Go! Move!
스콧, 이동해!!
Michael!
마이클! 글로 간다!
돌아서 갈 거야!
I'm coming to you! We'll go around!
Rebecca! To the river!
레베카, 강으로 가!
Rebecca! The river!
레베카, 강으로!!
- 썅
- 총 맞던지 보트로 가던지 알아서 해!
Fuck!
Well, go or don't go!
Your choice!
Move!
일어나, 어서!
Come on!
Go! Move!
스콧, 뛰어!!
Let's go! Run! Mike!
마이크!!
Fuck! All right!
Get on the 30-cal!
- 쌍
- 어서! 기관총 집어! 쟤 좀 도와줘요!
Help him in!
- 어서!
- 출발해!
Come on, go, go!
Fuckin' eat shit!
이거나 쳐먹어라 씨발!
Nice work, Aquaman!
잘했어, 도마뱀양반!
이제 집에 데려다 줘!
Now take us home!
Oh, come on! Are you
fuckin' kiddin' me?!
아, 뭐야?!
장난해 시발?!
Oh, shit!
아 시발!
- Ready, Martinez?
- You got it.
마르티네즈!
- 알았어!
- 지금, 지금!
Now! Now!
Fuckin' fire up
that 30-cal, Scott!
- 거기 기관총으로 조져, 스콧!
- 알았어!
I'm on it!
Fuckin' piece of shit!
개 씨발것들!!
Fuck! 30-cal's out.
썅! 총알 다 떨어짐!
- Mikey!
- Yeah?
- 마이키!
- 어?
I'm down to my sidearm.
How are you doing?
나 권총밖에 안 남았어, 그쪽은 어때?
Fuck! I'm losing power,
Scott! Losing power!
시동 꺼질라 칸다, 스콧! 시동 꺼질라 캐!
The engine's hit!
- 엔진에 맞았어!
- 플랜 B가 필요해, 스콧!
We need a Plan B, mates!
존나 좋네 시발
Fuckin' awesome!
You got any C4 left?
C4 남은 거 있어?
RPG 내놔, 어서!
- Get going on that next one.
- OK.
- 하나 더 만들어 줘!
- 알았어!
- Michael!
- Yeah?
- 마이클!
- 어!
Get down here!
이리와!
Martinez, throw me another mag!
마르티네즈, 탄창 하나 줘요!
Take the wheel.
- 조종대 맡아요!
- 네!
Got it.
All right! I throw, you shoot!
- 좋아! 내가 던지면, 니가 쏴!
- 1에 0에?
On one or zero?
Shut the fuck up and shoot it!
닥치고 그냥 쏴!
Shit!
- 썅!
- 썅!! 놓쳤잖아!
Fuck! You missed!
I can't believe you fuckin' missed!
어떻게 저걸 놓칠 수가 있어?!
You fuckin' throw it
right, I'll fuckin' hit it!
- 제대로 던져봐 씨발! 맞춰줄 테니까!
- 하! 해봐!
Go!
- Fuck you!
- Fuck, yeah!
Nice work, Michael.
잘했어, 마이클, 잘 쐈어!
폭탄 한번 잘 만들었어!
Nice shooting. Whoo!
Nice bomb-making.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
- 괜찮아?
- 어
Zero, this is Bravo Team.
본부! 여기는 브라보 팀, 들리나?
Do you read me?
Bravo, from Zero, good check, over.
브라보, 여기는 본부. 잘 들린다, 오버
상황 보고하라!
Sit-rep?
It's a little hairy.
We got the package.
- 아슬아슬하긴 했지만, 타겟을 확보했다
- 잘했다. 타겟 데리고 복귀하라
Good work. Bring him in.
Get down! Get down!
엎드려, 엎드려!
Get down! Shit!
- 엎드려, 엎드려!
- 장전!
Get us out of here!
어서 달려!
Oh, shit! Incoming!
온다!! 숙여!!!
Down!
Bravo, come in.
브라보, 나와라
브라보, 응답하라
Bravo Team, respond.
좋아
가자!
상업적 이용 금지, 수정 배포 금지
Vn